<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jahon Amir</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jahon Amir</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there!My name is Jahon. Pronounced Jahân or d͡ʒæhɒŋ, referring to the world, universe, or galaxy in Persian, Urdu, Dari and Sanskrit.
A ClueAlthough I was given this grandiose name, I never fully knew it’s meaning until much later in life. Growing up a lower-middle working class suburb just east of the city center of Sacramento, California, the common language was American English and that side of my family practiced the predominant culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/post/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/education/</guid>
      <description>I hold a top ranked bachelors and masters degree from the University of California, Berkeley and am pursuing a second masters from the University of California, Davis. I’ve researched at two universities abroad and hold a certificate in project management from the University of Adelaide.
University of California, DavisDepartment of Agriculture and Resource Economics
Master of Science, Energy Econometrics
2019 - 2020
Key CourseworkAppled EconometricsQuantitative MicroeconomicsGame TheoryNatural Resource EconomicsFinanceUniversity of California, BerkeleyGoldman School of Public Policy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>/post/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/experience/</guid>
      <description>Agricultural Issues CenterLawrence Berkeley National LaboratoryOpcondysStrategenCalifornia Public Utilities CommissionCalifornia Environmental Protection AgencyCity of Kalgoorlie-BoulderEnergy analyst, UC Berkeley MPP, and UC Davis MS Candidate with a background in energy finance, markets, greenhouse gas, and policy modeling and analysis. Experience includes:
Project finance and life-cycle greenhouse gas modeling
Cleantech and energy market and policy analysis
Strategy development for entering emerging markets and governance</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deliverables</title>
      <link>/post/deliverables/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/deliverables/</guid>
      <description>ES&amp;amp;T Publication: California Bioenergy Policy EvaluationES&amp;amp;T Publication: Role of Digestate and Biochar in Carbon-Negative Bioenergy.Task Report: Facility Lifecycle Emissions AnalysisMasters Thesis: Project Financial ModelCourse Project: The Effect of Raising the Minimum Wage on Teen EmploymentClient Project: Cleantech Market EvaluationClient Project: Storage Policy EvaluationCourse Project: Wholesale Electricity AuctionsClient Project: Regulatory EvaluationCourse Project: Quasi Experiments for the Bioenergy SectorCourse Project: Bioenergy Generation Least Cost PathHere you can see a selection of my work done over the years, in form of either code snippets, visualizations, or full publications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>